{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which sensor is used in magnetic levitation experiment?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Ultrasonic sensors",
        "b": "IR sensors",
        "c": "Hall effect sensors",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the disadvantage of proportional controller?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Provides a constant steady state error  ",
        "b": "Improves stability of the system",
        "c": "Improves steady state error",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following controllers improves steady state error and also stability of the system?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "P controller ",
        "b": "PI controller ",
        "c": "PD controller",
        "d": "All of the above "
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "A condition where integral control action drives the output of a controller into saturation is called",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Self-bias",
        "b": " Repeat  ",
        "c": "Wind-up",
        "d": " Noise "
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The controller output when the error is zero is known as",
      "answers": {
        "a": " Bias ",
        "b": "Error",
		"c": "Both the above",
        "d": "None of them"
        
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The magnetic force, responsible for magnetic levitation is__",
      "answers": {
        "a": "  Magnetic attraction force ",
        "b": " Magnetic repulsion force",
        "c": "None of these",
        "d": " Both of a and b"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The MAGLEV is a_____ plant",
      "answers": {
        "a": "SISO ",
        "b": "SIMO",
        "c": "MIMO",
        "d": " None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "The ________ part of a PID controller is very sensitive to noise",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Derivative ",
        "b": "Integral",
        "c": "Both a and b",
        "d": "None of the above "
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }, 
    {
      "question": "In a magnetic ball levitation system the ferromagnetic core coil acts as an actuator.",
      "answers": {
        "a": " True ",
        "b": "False"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "In a magnetic levitation system , the propulsion force is to , ",
      "answers": {
        "a": " Push moving part forward ",
        "b": " lift up the moving part",
        "c": " Both of the above ",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
  ]
}
